{
    "subject": "resource/101_Dalmatians_II:_Patch's_London_Adventure",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Kath_Soucie",
    "human_readable": "Kath Soucie stars in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9639072418212891,
            "question": "Who stars in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9103288054466248,
            "question": "What kind of adventure takes place in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9027228355407715,
            "question": "Where is the adventure set in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7951200008392334,
            "question": "What is the genre of '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6926924586296082,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie starring Kath Soucie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6591078042984009,
            "question": "In what film does Kath Soucie play a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4499830901622772,
            "question": "Is Kath Soucie known for voicing characters in animated films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25700271129608154,
            "question": "Are there other movies featuring Patch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1539805829524994,
            "question": "Who else might star in a movie about dogs going on an adventure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04313620179891586,
            "question": "Can you name other movies with animal protagonists?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kath Soucie stars in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7851_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who else might star in a movie about dogs going on an adventure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7851_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other movies featuring Patch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7851_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kath Soucie known for voicing characters in animated films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7851_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7851_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that, according to the context information, Kath Soucie voices Cadpig and Rolly in '101 Dalmatians: The Series', but there is no mention of her starring in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document containing the path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7851/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt` lists Kath Soucie as voicing Cadpig and Rolly in \"101 Dalmatians: The Series\" and mentions that she voiced Perdita from 101 Dalmatians since 101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure (2003). This confirms that Kath Soucie starred in '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Kath Soucie actually voices Perdita from 101 Dalmatians since 101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure (2003), but it is stated that she only voiced Cadpig, Rolly and Anita in 101 Dalmatians: The Series.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}